<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0">
   <channel>
      <description>Bloomengine | Arcadia Heights</description>
      <title>Bloomengine | Arcadia Heights</title>
      <generator>Bloomengine</generator>
      <link>https://bloomengine.com/arcadia_heights/source_code/index.html?f=E4awJsC2A+DOAuBDY85JdAnJ6BGb0ADEScWadAMx424XkAeFdALBU3Y9Ez9AGz8aXOnV5juE8cU4VqI2tKrQATLWqLym9vWigIMLcSblcxIA&amp;ampi=IwH1AYU0Kt9EA&amp;ampsource=feedburner_email</link>
      <item>
         <title>Bloomengine | Arcadia Heights</title>
         <description>
            <p>Hello Everyone, Hope you're all doing good. Thanks for signing up for updates. There's a few new scenes added to the game. You can jump directly to the new content by clicking <a href="https://bloomengine.com/arcadia_heights/source_code/index.html?f=E4awJsC2A+DOAuBDY85JdAnJ6BGb0ADEScWadAMx424XkAeFdALBU3Y9Ez9AGz8aXOnV5juE8cU4VqI2tKrQATLWqLym9vWigIMLcSblcxIA&i=IwH1AYU0Kt9EA&source=feedburner_email">here</a></p><p>Here is also some character art:</p><p><img src="https://bloomengine.com/i/180811_chess_club.png" /></p><p><p>Background info: the Chess Club is an offically registered school club founded in the beginning under the supervision of the Board of Education.</p> 
            <p>Focus of the club: Chess-playing and friendly competition. Cultivating chess chic aesthetic. Turf wars with rival clubs. </p>
            <p>Dress for chess: School uniform jackets turned inside out. Close-cropped hair and socks tucked overtop pant legs. Knee-high socks and skirts. </p>
            <p>Grandmaster: Club coordinator. Qualties required for this leadership role include attention to detail, interpersonal skills and proficiency in bare-knuckle brawling. The Grandmaster is a member of the Hardcore.</p>
            <p>The Hardcore: Members of the club's inner circle. Upon achieving the rank of Hardcore through winning a few chess games, social popularity and brawling, the member's hair turns white. (This phenomenon occurs with all high-ranking members of school clubs).</p>
            <p>Boardmaster: Person who keeps chessboard strapped to their back.</p>
            <p>Ceremonial chessboard: Custom-built chessboard with immovable pieces. Symbolic meaning and purpose forgotten. Kept in the presence of Hardcore when they convene.</p></description>
         <link>https://bloomengine.com/arcadia_heights/source_code/index.html?f=E4awJsC2A+DOAuBDY85JdAnJ6BGb0ADEScWadAMx424XkAeFdALBU3Y9Ez9AGz8aXOnV5juE8cU4VqI2tKrQATLWqLym9vWigIMLcSblcxIA&amp;ampi=IwH1AYU0Kt9EA&amp;ampsource=feedburner_email</link>
         <guid>180811</guid>
      </item>
   </channel>
</rss>
